You'll join the training camp in
late February after the New Year.
The assessment is in early June.
Enrollment in early July.
You sound like I'm guaranteed
to pass the assessment.
Doesn't my son have what it takes?
Thanks, Old Xu.
They broke up a long time ago.
What about these two?
[Changyang's evil little sister is
on the phone with a fortune teller]
They're together.
Pick two more numbers between 1 and 45.
Hmm.
23 and 27.
The two people you just
thought of are twin flames.
What does that mean?
Look it up yourself.
The two of them came from a certain
place with a mission to be here.
So their meeting was inevitable,
not a coincidence.
Ah, I won't say anymore.
I can't reveal too many heavenly secrets.
Then how can I make them break up?
And get him back
together with the other guy?
Keep the three of them in your mind,
and pick three more numbers from 1 to 45.
2.
Hmm, 35, and 7.
Well, looking at the current
situation, it's not hard.
You can temporarily get you what you want.
But no matter what you do,
it won't change the final outcome.
[Robo-narration explaining true love and fate
playing in the backround for some reason]
That's fine, just tell me what to do.
Just use your current identities.
Your dual identity in reality and online.
But there's one thing you
need to be careful about.
Look at this Persona card.
They can't be completely exposed.
Otherwise, you'll be doomed as well.
[The most important goal is unity, not only in
terms of emotions or lifestyle,
but also in a harmonious
and positive collaboration
to achieve a higher level
of universal love together.]
"A Winter Sun Wakes the Wind in Spring Hills' Dream"
[People encounter different
soulmates at different stages of life,
but each soul will only
have one twin flame.]
(Episode 10: Filling the tower)
Brother.
When are you bringing
my sister-in-law back again?
Last time you came home for dinner,
didn't you hide?
That was my first time meeting
him, I was just too nervous!
Oh, come on, brother.
I promise if you bring him back again,
I definitely won't hide.
We'll see.
["From Today The Sun Sets At
The South Tower" begins shooting]
Pick one.
Hand me that sleep mask.
I'll hold it down, you read it.
The wind and rain darken the sky,
The roosters crow without end.
Now that I have seen my lord,
How could I not be overjoyed?
You can do one more line.
Are you collecting my voice?
For my navigation.
Did you see your lord today?
Can you put some emotion into it?
Pretty good.
I mean, it's pretty good.
I can't see!
I'm going to fall!
Ah!
When are you going to the
training camp after the New Year?
Late February.
For three months?
Yeah.
Once youI pass the assessment, you'll enroll.
Getting answers out of
you is like pulling teeth.
Reporting to the boss.
Training camp from March to June.
Enrollment in late July.
Are you sure you'll pass?
Doesn't your husband have what it takes?
Get lost.
Don't move.
[Feng Lizhen is calling]
My mom is calling me.
Hi, brother, sister-in-law, Happy New Year!
Why is it you?
Where are you guys right now?
Manyin Village. What about you?
We just arrived in Nanlu.
Why don't you two come over
and ring in the New Year with us?
No way. Your
sister-in-law is a firecracker.
She blows up wherever she goes.
Fine.
Hey, hello, Xiaoxiao.
Sister-in-law! Sister-in-law!
Happy New Year, sister-in-law!
I'm bowing to wish you a Happy
New Year. One bow, two bows...
Stop.
Three bows...
You're definitely up to no good.
Just take good care of the two elders.
Yes, sir! Mission guaranteed
to be accomplished!
Hanging up.
Ah.
That new show your company is producing,
aren't you going to act in it?
I can't.
A cameo in the spin-off is one thing,
but my character has a
romance arc in the main series.
With a guy or a girl?
Same as you.
Because of me, you don't take romance roles anymore?
I won't take them while we're together.
Can't you just say you'll never
take them for the rest of your life?
Fine.
Senior Brother.
Let us part.
And after we part?
We go our separate ways and live well.
Cut!
Awesome, awesome!
That scene was incredible!
What was that singing
in the valley just now?
A poem written to the God
of Death by the Manyin people.
It's chanted by the
high priest of the village.
They chant it every New
Year's Eve to pray for blessings.
Praying to the God of Death?
They believe that death is life.
Without death, there is no new life.
Hey, two of you, head over there.
Can we ask the priest to
record this chant for us?
Come on.
Sure.
I want to go see Sister Lan.
Do you really want to?
Seeing that cloud
suddenly reminded me of her.
I shouldn't have said anything.
There's no such thing as
a straight path to the end.
I thought going to Camellia
Village would be on the way to Xigui.
People always fail because
of their own assumptions.
Excuse me, ma'am!
We want to get out of this mountain road.
How do we get to the highway?
Go straight ahead.
There's a Tea God Temple
there with a fork in the road.
Okay, thank you, ma'am.
You're welcome.
Excuse me, sir, how do we
get to the Tea God Temple?
Go this way.
We just passed the Tea God Temple.
You couldn't tell from the outside wall.
We both missed it.
What are they singing?
A poem written to the God
of Death by the Manyin people.
It's chanted by the
high priest of the village.
Every New Year's Day,
they chant it to pray for blessings.
Praying to the God of Death?
They believe that death is life.
Without death, there is no new life.
A very simple sense of reverence.
Happy New Year, Sister.
Happy New Year, Sister Jialin.
Look at the trending topics.
(Your sister-in-law is a firecracker.
She blows up wherever she goes.)
["Feng Qinglang's suspected boyfriend"
+ a recording evil little sister made]
Is this your sister?
Yes.
At least she knew to cover your face.
You two need to be careful.
This video was posted by
someone named Wajijilu.
I had someone look into it.
They're a veteran shipper
of Hao Qing Wan Zhong.
If it is your sister, you'll
have to look that up yourself.
I'll suppress this trending topic for now.
Is it Xiaoxiao?
She also posted something else.
It's a photo from when I brought
you home for dinner last time.
Hello, the number you
dialed is not answering.
Please try again later.
If the original video leaks,
will your enrollment
qualification be revoked?
I haven't even taken the assessment yet.
What enrollment qualification?
Sister Lan, you once told
me to be brave in love,
but also to take
responsibility for my actions.
Does that mean love isn't
about ignoring the consequences?
If love requires calculating
the consequences,
it's no longer pure.
Is it still love if it's not pure?
Xu Luxiao, you must be sick in the head.
You're the one who's sick!
You purposely made a video
call to record it, didn't you?
I'll do whatever I want.
Give Hao Qing Wan Zhong back to me!
You're a freaking college student now!
Don't you have any brains at all?
[He's deleting a message from Secretary Li
stating the original video has been removed]
We're not going to Camellia Village.
We're going home.
Okay.
I just can't get into character, Director.
Well, try looking at it from another angle.
If your lover kept something from you,
and you eventually found
out you were being used,
while they kept insisting
it was for your own good.
Come on, Haoyu, give us a look of betrayal.
Ah.
Yeah, feel it the way I described.
We'll try another take in a bit.
If it really doesn't
work, we'll shoot it last.
Thanks, Director.
Lu, your portrayal of Nanlou is too bitter.
[Conversation with Tian Guoguo]
The other day when you
two shot the valley scene,
I could tell you caught real feelings.
Brother Guo is warning you,
don't get in too deep.
[Risk agreement]
Qi Haoyu is bad news.
You know perfectly well he's using you.
He's playing you like a tool.
Don't take it seriously.
Just have fun and leave it at that.
Coming.
Then you might as well kill me too!
I still have me!
I've known everything from start to finish.
I know the most!
Nanlou, Nanlou, calm down!
Everything I did was for you!
Cut!
Good.
Playback.
Okay.
That's a wrap!
That's a wrap for this scene!
Great work, everyone.
Bro, let me borrow your phone.
Why? Want to see the behind-the-scenes?
I saw you recording the
playback earlier. Let me see.
Here.
Guo!
Coming, Brother Long!
It's not hot, here.
Not bad acting.
Right?
Really.
That's what I'm saying.
Ah.
Come find me for your next project.
I'll definitely find you.
I'll definitely find you for the next one.
Let me tell you...
You're going to the training
camp right when I'm away.
Even if I were there,
you wouldn't dare come.
Who wouldn't dare?
A good brother seeing you off.
Who's your good brother?
Fine.
Then I'll wear women's clothes.
I'll cross-dress to see you off.
No days off for three months?
I don't know.
Come down.
Come up.
I just found my bag.
Don't lose yourself.
What's wrong?
I want to stay in character for
the scenes these next few days.
Man, acting like this will
give you schizophrenia.
Why are you here?
Your father needed me for something.
I'll wait for you downstairs.
This is our third time meeting.
[Changyang's submission form]
The higher-ups received a report letter.
Citing Changyang's orientation, they
revoked his training camp qualification.
Wasn't the original video deleted?
Not everything relies on the truth.
If someone reports it, someone
else will want to avoid the trouble.
Is there any room to salvage this?
I'll try to fight for him again.
But time and time again,
there won't be a third chance.
I understand.
I'll draw a clear line with him.
Uncle.
You win.
Qingtian wants to participate
in that documentary.
Are you going to support your brother?
Use your phone to call Xu Luxiao.
What's wrong?
I've acted with you so many times,
now act with me for once.
Are you at home?
Can you get a shot of downstairs at
Wenshu's place from your second floor?
Take the photos and wait for my word.
If you want to see the
Hao-Qing ship make a comeback,
don't post the photos online.
This is great!
My ship is coming back to life, oh my god!
Xu Luxiao, what rumors
are you spreading now?
I'm just shipping my couple.
How is that any of your business?
It is.
You sank my ship.
We are sworn enemies.
Are you crazy?
If you spread rumors again,
I'll report your account.
You...!
Just you wait!
[Shi Yuhao calling]
You know Changyang's training
camp qualification got revoked, right?
You did this?
I've always thought you owed me.
Bullshit.
When you sank the ship back then,
you and Sister Lan
weren't exactly sitting idle.
You were the one who played dirty first.
It's like boxing.
It takes a punch from you and a
punch from me to make a fight.
Well, I still have some good stuff on hand.
I asked you out before
and you didn't believe me.
Like I was making
things up out of thin air.
Now you know.
I'll send you another picture.
Think again about
whether you want to see me.
[Shi Yuhao sending a screenshot
of a conversation with Wajijilu]
[My brother brought Lang Di back home, are
things really done between the two of you?]
[I can help you get him back]
Set the time and place and send them to me.
You notify the paparazzi.
Your acting's pretty good.
I didn't win Best Actor for nothing.
Bring out the evidence you have.
And your terms?
The Hao-Qing ship makes a comeback.
I can't guarantee you'll be popular again,
but I'll cooperate however I need to.
Straightforward. Here.
A work photo.
The major shareholder of
Chunshan Su is Feng Lizhen's niece.
Xu Changyang also has
shares in Chunshan Su.
His half-brother, Wenshu,
was the investor for your last movie.
Their shared father, Xu Jinbai,
I don't know how much money
he laundered through this company.
And I can't find out.
But how much sky-high priced
tea was purchased through him?
Anyone who wants to
investigate can definitely find out.
Do you know why Xu Jinbai
would rather let Xu Changyang
bear the title of an illegitimate child
than divorce his first wife?
Because he's afraid.
He's afraid these dirty deals
behind the scenes will be exposed.
And the internet has
no shortage of sleuths.
I went through a lot of hoops to
get this photo from a focus puller.
It really doesn't prove much.
But the Xu family really
can't stand up to scrutiny.
And the path Xu Changyang wants to take
really can't weather the storms
of the entertainment industry.
Kicking him out
is good for everyone.
Today's material is enough for you to use.
Coordinate with my company
regarding the variety show.
What's wrong?
What, what, what's going on?
Mom, my ship has back to life!
I'm so happy, Mom!
Ah, good.
As long as you're happy.
Why are you crying?
That trending topic online
was suppressed a long time ago.
A video with a blocked face
doesn't prove anything either.
The one you just saw in the video,
the actor officially
announced a variety show.
It definitely has nothing
to do with the kid.
Ah, okay.
I'll pass it on to the boss.
Thank you for your trouble.
It's fine.
Go warn that person.
Understood.
The boss knows you've investigated a lot.
Know when to stop.
You should know what that means.
I do.
Did you find my teapot?
I'll be downstairs in a bit.
Bring it out to me.
Teapots are everywhere.
Just buy one at the airport.
Mind your own business.
I'll be there in five minutes.
Get ready to come downstairs.
Stop the car.
My world is a raging storm.
We're not in the same world.
Let's go back to square one.
Call Sister Jialin.
The Chunshan Su music
video can't be broadcast.
Terminate the contract.
I'll cover the compensation.
It's my first time seeing you like this.
Like a stray dog caught in the rain.
Why use a dog to describe Changyang?
Mom, you don't get it.
Calling him the queen's dog
is a compliment.
Who's the queen?
My brother.
I don't understand you kids.
I say go upstairs
and take a hot shower,
then change into some clean clothes.
You need to respect your own body.
Go, you're dripping
wet and ruining my sofa.
Careful.
What's wrong with them?
Angsty romance.
Explain it to Mom properly.
Mom doesn't understand this internet slang.
Grandma definitely gets it.
Yangyang, take your medicine.
What do you want to eat?
Auntie will make it for you.
Your husband is running
a fever in your bed.
Cut off all trade relations
with Chunshan Su.
Understood.
The music video Qinglang
shot for Chunshan Su earlier...
His company has already
refunded the endorsement fee.
Are the accounts clean?
Spotless.
Make sure all the footage
is completely scrubbed.
Got it, I'll send someone to handle it.
Pour me a glass of water.
You didn't orchestrate this whole incident,
but you definitely catalyzed it.
From the moment you appointed
Qinglang as the ambassador,
your pieces were already in motion.
If my guess is correct,
you must have also shown him
the photos Shi Yuhao
took while stalking us.
The fact that Shi Yuhao convinced
him to join the variety show
proves he has more evidence in his hands.
The photo of him and
Shi Yuhao that trended,
he intentionally leaked it to the media.
Terminating the contract with Chunshan Su
proves he's protecting you.
And he's protecting me, too.
See for yourself.
Your application for the
training camp was revoked.
This is a second chance I
pulled strings to get for you.
So you told him about this, too.
Changyang.
Selfishly speaking,
you are the child I value the most.
I don't want to suppress
any of your dreams.
Even if it means going
to the Hunter School,
where life and death are unpredictable,
I still want to support
you in achieving your goals.
Unselfishly speaking,
your qualities in many areas far
exceed those of ordinary people.
You can see the big
picture through the details,
and focus on the details
within the big picture.
You shouldn't waste your talent.
And he doesn't want you to waste it either.
This is the last chance you can seize.
[The two couplets on the side talk about the
sensory pleasures of reading and being alone]
What's been up with you lately?
You haven't been coming to my room.
The latter half of the
show is pretty stifling.
If you're feeling stifled, come to me.
I guarantee I'll help you let it all out.
I want to stay in character.
So beautiful.
Hey, handsome!
Look over here!
Nice!
Hold up the lantern.
[All the Weibo trending topics
are about BL actors and their shows]
Cut! Next!
Bring the lantern over here.
Let's get a close-up.
Okay.
A little to the left, a bit higher.
Both of you, look over here.
Hey, that's fantastic!
Haojue, stand up.
Yes, right, look at each other.
Wrap!
Yeah! Happy wrap!
Happy wrap!
Good, look over here.
Come on, look at me.
So handsome, looking good!
Beautiful, beautiful!